DAN HUMPHRIES

WWW.AUFBAU.IO // DAN@AUFBAU.IO Haggerston \diamond London \diamond UK

PROFILE SUMMARY

Fullstack software engineer. Specialised in creative and technical engineering. Ethical and sustainable roles only.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Software & Tools Languages: Python // JavaScript // SQL // C/C++ // MATLAB

Front-end: Svelte // Three JS // Vue // React // Next // D3 // p5
Back-end: Supabase // Flask // Docker // PostgreSQL // MongoDB
Full-stack: GCP // AWS // Linux // GraphQL // Blender // Web GL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aufbau Digital

Founder // Web Engineer

October 2022 - Present

London, UK

- · Creative Web Engineering // Bespoke Websites, Systems, and Apps. // Engineering, Development, and Design.
- · Tech Stack: Three JS // Svelte // Supabase // Rust // C/C++ // Web GPU

Midnight Studio

Web Engineer (Contract)

March 2022 - September 2022

London, UK

- · Fullstack engineer within a digital product agency. Highly autonomous position among technical leads.
- · Supporting technical clients including a leading IoT systems agency and a number of digital design projects.
- · Tech Stack: Svelte // React // Three JS // Next // Vercel // Docker // CMS

Hexis

November 2021 - February 2022

London, UK

Fullstack Developer (Contract)

- · Fullstack developer. Contracted to take start-up app from prototype to app store release. Scoped, hired, and led a react native developer and a junior developer to deliver a robust and scalable application within 4 months.
- · Tech Stack: React Native // Next // GCP // Apollo // GraphQL // Docker // Firebase

Kubrick Group

Machine Learning Engineer

November 2018 - August 2021

 $Reading,\ UK$

- · Engineer and co-architect on a microservice based data network & machine learning platform. Bespoke system enabled large multinational to run machine learning models on data assets stored across continents using existing internal server architecture. Within 6 months had become co-engineer & architect on project with senior mentor.
- · Tech Stack: Python // Vue // Flask // Celery // Docker // PostgreSQL // MongoDB // CUDA // Linux

EDUCATION

University College London

MSci Neuroscience (2:1 Hons)

September 2014 - May 2018

London, UK

- · Course of study focused on Computational Neuroscience and Dynamic Systems.
- · Masters Dissertation: 'Dendritic Spine Stability during Regulative Homeostasis' with Prof Tara Keck
- · Bachelors Dissertation: 'Neural Oscillatory Rhythms: Physics & Function' with Dr Lorenzo Fabrizi

Kings College London

MA Philosophy (Merit)

September 2021 - September 2022

London, UK

- · Course of study focused on Kant, Mind, Communication, and Representation.
- · Masters Dissertation: 'Carving the Mind at its Joints' with Prof Bill Brewer

RESEARCH PROJECTS

University College London

Research Assistant

October 2022 - Present London, UK

- · Working with Dr Alexandra Constantinescu and Prof Neil Burgess to analyse 7T fMRI spatial navigation data.
- · Processing and analysing grid-cell and place-cell activity data. Custom scripts in MATLAB.

University Of Oxford

Research Assistant

July 2021 - Present $Oxford,\ UK$

- · Creating a mental state tracking tool with Dr Dan Joyce, a computational and clinical psychiatrist.
- · Lightweight and customisable tool to facilitate psychiatric research on the dynamics of mental state over time.

OTHER

Bartlett School of Architecture

July 2021 - September 2022

 $London,\ UK$

Computational Soul: Guest Seminar

- · Invited to run guest seminar on 'computational soul' as part of the Xalon Digital-Communities lecture series.
- · Discussed the notions of soul and representation in objects, and what it takes to synthesise 'computational soul'.